Make every second count.
Source Code is a thriller, science fiction,
mystery film directed by Duncan Jones.
When decorated soldier Captain Colter Stevens wakes up in the body of an unknown man, he
discovers he's part of a mission to find the bomber of a Chicago commuter train.
Colter Stevens, played by Jake Gyllenhaal.
Christina Warren, played by Michelle Monaghan.
Colleen Goodwin, played by Vera Farmiga.
Dr. Rutledge, played by Jeffrey Wright.
Derek Frost, played by Michael Arden.
Hazmi, played by Cas Anvar.
Source Code is a 2011 science fiction action thriller film
directed by Duncan Jones and written by Ben Ripley.
It stars Jake Gyllenhaal as a US Army officer who is sent into an eight-minute virtual re-creation of a
real-life train explosion, and tasked with determining the identity of the terrorist who bombed it.
Michelle Monaghan, Vera Farmiga, and Jeffrey Wright play supporting roles.
It had its world premiere on March 11, 2011, at South by Southwest and was released by
Summit Entertainment on April 1, 2011, in North America and Europe.
It received positive reviews from critics and was a box office
success, grossing $147.3 million on a $31.9 million budget.
The film explores themes of race against time, bomb,
virtual reality, identity, investigation.
The tone is intense and thought_provoking and mind_bending.